DAN KLEIN: So when you want breadth
research, you want it when the
solutions are kind of not too far.
So what you're trying to find is
connected to you by a relatively
shallow solution.
And then it's not so expensive to
try all the shallow things.
Whereas depth research tries
these crazy long plans that
may not even work.
So if your solutions are relatively
shallow, breadth
research is a good answer.
When you care about the length, breadth
research has a guarantee that
depth research does not.
How about the opposite?
When might you care about
depth research?
In general, you're going to prefer depth
research in cases where you want
to get to the bottom of the graph.
That could be because the graph
isn't actually very deep.
It could be because the solutions are
all down there at the bottom.
So if you remember the cartoon where the
gems in the mountain, if they're
all at the bottom and you need to get
to the bottom anyway, you might as
well go straight there and
hope for the best, right?
So there are a lot of trade offs.
We're going to see cases where about
breadth research is better and where
depth research is better.